Yes, hello.
はい、こんにちは
I'm nervous.
緊張しますね
It's cute.
可愛いね
A little small.
少し小さい
Cashier?
キャシャ?
thin.
細い
It looks like it's going to break.
折れそうだよね
Isn't it Cashier?
キャシャじゃないですか
Did you play any sports?
スポーツなんかしてたの?
You don't play sports, do you?
スポーツはしてないでしょ
It's not like you can't sunbathe.
太陽浴びちゃいけないとかそうじゃないよね
Isn't that so?
そうじゃないの?
I guess that's not the case.
一応そうではないのね
I don't think I should take a bath in the sun.
太陽浴びちゃいけないとかね
If the tooth on the branch I can see from the window falls off, my life will end.
窓から見える枝にある歯が散ったら私の命も終わるみたいな
That's not true.
そうじゃないですよね
違いますね
What are you doing now?
今何やってるんですか?
Currently a vocational student.
今専門学生
That's nice.
いいですね
Learning.
学びはね
It's tough right now due to Corona.
今コロナ大変だからね
I don't really understand school anymore either.
学校もよくわからなくなってますよね
By the way, do you have a boyfriend now?
ちなみに今、彼氏はいるんですか?
I have a boyfriend.
彼氏います
I'm jealous.
羨ましいなぁ
How many times a week do you go on dates?
デートは週に何回くらいやってます?
With my boyfriend.
彼 氏と
Dates are 3 days a week.
デートは週3日
3 days a week.
週3日
Do you mean you do it about 3 days a week?
週3日くらいしてるってこと?
different?
違う?
Maybe so.
そうかも
そうかもね
I don't know if that's the case.
そうかもわかんないよね
そうじゃないかもわかんない
It's a mystery.
謎ってことでね
It's mysterious.
ミステリアスね
By the way, what?
ちなみにね、あれ?
How old are you?
お年が?
I'm 20 years old now.
今20歳です
You're 20 years old, right?
20歳ですよね
She's 20 years old, which means she has a boyfriend.
20歳ってことで彼氏がいるということですけど、
How long ago was your first experience?
初体験なんかいつくらいでした?
My first experience was when I was 17 years old.
初体験は17歳でした
Huh?
あれ?
Isn't it a little early?
ちょっと早くない?
17 years old?
17歳?
17 years old.
17歳
Who is the other person?
相手は誰?
The opponent is a senior.
相手は先輩
father?
お 父さん?
No.
違うよ
senior?
先輩?
He's my senior.
俺のと先輩だよ
picture?
え?
Does that mean it's high school?
って言ってたら高校なの?
We're seniors from the same high school.
同じ高校の先輩ね
picture?
え?
Does that mean we weren't dating?
付き合ってなかったってこと?
We weren't dating...we were dating.
付き合ってな...付き合ってたけど
what?
何?
Weren't you dating?
付き合ってなかったんでしょ?
Does that mean he's not your boyfriend?
彼氏じゃないってこと?
what?
何?
Which one?
どっちどっち?
We were dating.
付き合ってた
Were you dating?
付き合ってた?
Boyfriend?
彼氏ね?
Your senior & boyfriend?
先輩で&彼氏ね?
Yes, yes, yes.
はい はいはい
Where was the location?
場所はどこでした?
The location is at home.
場所はおうち
Home.
おうち
Please make the address a little more detailed.
ちょっと住所細かくしてください
Which one?
どっちのうち?
picture?
え?
Over there.
向こうの
Over there?
向こうのうち?
picture?
え?
So, you were going to your senior's house, right?
ということはさ、先輩の家に行くってなってたわけでしょ?
I'm already full of motivation.
もうやる気満々じゃん
Does that mean you can definitely do it?
それはもう絶対やられるってことでしょ?
You had no choice but to go there, right?
む し ろやらないに行ったわけでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
different?
違う?
picture?
え?
a little bit.
ちょっと
there were?
あった?
When I first experienced it at that senior's house,
その先輩の家で初体験したときに、
Were the senior's parents in the house?
その家には先輩のご両親はいたのかな?
One time at a time.
一度一回とかに
there was?
いた?
there was.
いた
Were you there?
いたの?
Were you about to do that over your mom and dad's heads?
お父さんとお母さんの頭の上でそろそろそうしてたの?
yes.
そう
Hey?
ねえ?
Mom and dad were making tea and drinking roasted green tea while making tea.
お父さんとお母さんが茶がして、茶がしくりながらほうじ茶飲んで
We had sex once, right?
る ときにセックスしちゃったことでしょ?
Isn't it amazing?
すごいじゃないですか
Yes, yes, yes.
はい はいはい
I'm a high school student now.
今のが高校生ですからね
I'm very interested in it.
興味いっぱいいますもんね
By the way, there may be rumors about her current boyfriend.
ちなみに、その今の彼氏のうわきもあるかも
There might be.
あるかも
Male experience.
男性経験ね
How many men have you experienced in total?
男性経験トータルで何人ですか?
There are 2 people in total.
トータルで2人です
Are you safe?
無事で?
2 people?
2人?
So, that's it.
ということは、ということはあれですよ
I'm the third man.
僕、第三の男ですよ
It sounds like the title of a movie.
なんか映画のタイトルみたいですよ
He becomes the third man.
第三の男になっちゃうんですよ
I agree.
そうですね
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
I see.
そうか
Maybe my boyfriend or something like that 17 year senior is more me than anything.
たぶん、彼氏とかね、その17歳の先輩も何かよりも僕、
He's an old man.
おっちゃんですよ
Yeah, yeah.
うん、うん
Hey, are you okay?
ねえ、大丈夫ですか?
Do you like sex?
エッチは好きなの?
Naughty, I like it.
エッチ、好き
Do you like sex?
エッチは好き?
Look at the camera, do you like sex?
カメラ見ていって、エッチは好き?
Yeah, yeah.
うん、うん
I like sex.
エッチは好き
Ah, you like sex.
あ、エッチ好きなのね
By the way, is there the same person?
ちなみに同じ人ある?
Eh.
えー
There is, right?
あるでしょ?
A strange man right now.
今のはえーがおかしい男
Isn't it the same?
同じあるでしょ?
How, yeah.
どう、うん
Yeah.
うん
yeah?
ん?
What what?
なになに?
be?
ある?
How can some women be the same?
女には、どうやって同じ人いるの?
Fingers, yeah, and toys,
フィンガーとかさ、うん、あとトイス、
Toys.
トイス
Er, finger.
えー、フィンガー
Finger?
フィンガー?
Finger, finger.
フィンガーね、フィンガーね
It's not Toys.
トイスじゃないのね
It's not an adult toy.
アダルトトイスじゃないのね
By the way, do you have any adult toys?
あれ、ちなみにアダルトトイス持ってる?
I don't have it.
持ってない
Oh, you don't have it?
あ、持ってないのか
parents' home?
実家?
Maybe.
もしかして
Yeah.
うん
Oh, my parents' house?
あ、実家か
That's impossible.
そりゃ無理だね
But you know, it's small, you know, if it had a pink rotor or something like that,
でも小さいほら、ね、こうピンクローターとかだったら、
Well, I don't know if I can press the awakening button.
ま、覚醒を押せるかも分かんないじゃん
Do you understand?
分かる?
Yeah.
うん
It's a little difficult to do with an electric massager though.
電気マッサージ機だとはちょっと難しいけど
But that's why you use your fingers.
でも、だから指でね
Yes, yes.
はいはい
It means that women like it too.
女にも好きと、いうことですね
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
Well, it's okay if I say something like that, right?
え、そういうこと言ったらいいんですよね?
Yeah.
うん
Eh, you like women, right?
え、女に好きでしょ?
There are very few people who do it reluctantly even after telling a woman that they don't like it.
女に嫌いですって言いながらしぶしぶやってる人もなかなかいない
Because it is.
です からね
I agree.
そうですね
Yeah.
うん
I don't know if there are times when I hate sex and have to do it reluctantly.
セックス嫌いでしぶしぶやることあるかも分かりませんけど、
There's no one who does it reluctantly because they don't like it.
女に嫌いでしぶしぶやる人いませんからね
Well, I guess I have to do something about it.
じゃあやんなきゃいいじゃんって話ですから
yes.
はい
Well, I'm a little concerned,
で、ちょっとね、ちょっと気になるんですけど、
It's such a stender thing.
すっごいステンダーだよね
How many cup breasts?
おっぱい何カップ?
Breasts, shay cups.
おっぱい、シェイカップ
Ah, it's here.
あ、ここあるね
Please stand for a moment.
ちょっと立ってごらんなさい
Stand up, stand up.
立って立って
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
Well, you know, it's bad if it gets dirty.
で、ちょっとその、ね、汚れちゃうとまずいから、
Hey, what should I do with this? What does it mean?
ね、これなにどうしよう、どういうこと?
This kind of designer.
こういう、こういうデザイナーね
yes.
そう
hey.
ね
That's right.
そうだよね
It's not like there aren't buttons.
ボタンがないわけじゃないんだよね
There are no buttons.
ボタンはない
From the beginning.
最初から
It's buttonless.
ボタンレスなのね
Yes, yes.
はいはいね
Okay, let's just press this button.
じゃ、ちょっとこの、ね、このボタンをね、
Can I have you take it off in order?
順番に外していってもらっていい?
hey.
ね
Isn't it nice that there are fewer buttons?
いいじゃないですか、ボタン少なくて
hey.
ね
Easy to take off.
脱ぎやすい
What do you think?
どうなんですか?
I'm going to have sex today.
今日エッチするって
Yeah.
うん
You were just thinking, weren't you?
思ってただけでしょ?
I received a DM yesterday too.
昨日とかもDM来て
Yeah.
うん
You thought we were going to have sex tomorrow, right?
明日エッチするんだって思ってたんでしょ?
How are you doing today?
どうですか、今日?
Did you sleep properly?
ちゃんと寝れました?
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張して
Were you nervous?
緊張した?
Yeah, I was nervous too.
そうか、俺も緊張した
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
Well, this is good.
さ、いいっすね、これ
I took it off.
脱いちゃいました
Yes, yes, yes.
はいはいはい
Oh, it's beautiful, beautiful.
あ、綺麗な綺麗なね
That's a long time.
手長いね
手長いっすね
Yeah.
うん
There you go, Sicup.
ほらね、シカップ
hey.
ね
This is a skirt.
これはスカートね
This, just this.
これ、ちょっとこれ
How do I take it?
どうやって取るの?
behind?
後ろ?
Ah, that's fine, that's fine.
あ、いいじゃん、いいじゃん
Just a little, it's going to get dirty.
ちょっと、ちょっとね、汚れちゃいますからね
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、はいはいはい
Wow.
うわ
Is it something like this serow?
なんですか、このカモシカのような
Why did you take off your socks?
なんで靴下取ったの?
picture?
え?
It's fine, it's fine.
いいよ、別にいいよ
Uncool?
格好悪い?
I took the sock from my belly.
腹から靴下取ったの
Yeah.
うん
Yes, okay, I'll take it, I'll take it.
はい、いいよ、いただきます、いただきますね
Oh, that's amazing, take a look at this.
あ、すごいじゃん、ちょっとこれ
A little more in the middle.
もうちょい真ん中に真ん中に
Wow.
うわ
Are you eating?
飯食ってる?
I'm eating.
食べてます
What do you like?
何が好き?
food.
食べ物
Hmm, sushi.
うーん、お寿司
It's not meat.
肉じゃないんだ
It's healthy.
ヘルシーなものね
It's not meat.
肉じゃないね
What do you like about sushi?
お寿司の何が好きなの?
salmon roe.
イクラ
salmon roe?
イクラ?
Is it fish eggs?
魚卵ですか?
Is it fish egg type?
魚卵系ですか?
魚卵系
That's amazing.
すごいね
If you eat a lot.
ガリガリ食べるとね
I don't know if it could be ventilation.
通風になるかもわかんないね
If you eat too much fish eggs.
あんまり魚卵食ってるとね
Yes, yes.
はい はい
So, the Holy Fleet was getting bigger.
で、聖艦隊大きくなわせてました
Holy fleet.
聖艦隊
Where is the Holy Fleet?
聖艦隊どこですかね?
Holy fleet.
聖艦隊
Hmm, Saint Jin Corps?
ん ー、聖jin隊?
tits.
おっぱい
tits?
おっぱい?
Breasts.
おっぱいね
What can I do to make my breasts feel good?
おっぱいどうすると気持ちいいのかな?
Breasts.
おっつっぱい
What can I do to make my breasts feel better?
おつっぱいどうすると 気持ちいいのかな?
When you are squeezed.
ギュッてされると
What if you get squeezed?
ギュッとされると?
Doesn't it feel good when your breasts are squeezed?
おつっぱいをギュッとされると気持ちよくね?
Yes, yes.
はい はい
So, what about other than boobs?
じゃあ、おつっぱい以外は?
Just breasts?
おつっぱいだけ?
Other than my boobs, my neck.
おつっぱい以外は、首
head?
首?
What should I do with my neck?
首どうされていいの?
Neck.
ネックね
What should I do about the neck?
ネックをどうしたらいいのかね
I have to know.
知らないとね
It becomes a bit of a bottleneck.
ちょっとネックになりますから
I'd say it's you.
お前かと言うね
My neck is getting really rough.
首を、すごいサワサワされる
My neck is so stiff as I squeeze my boobs.
おっぱいをギューって首はサワサワなんだ
Yes, yes.
はいはい
What else?
他には?
Oh, there it is.
え、そこだ
Is that the only point of achievement?
成果の点、そこだけなの?
Does it fit here?
ここで収まってんの?
What else?
他には?
Bottom, butt.
下の方、お尻
Butt?
お尻?
Is it your butt?
お尻なの?
where?
どこ?
Please tell me something properly.
ちょっと教えてちゃんと
where?
ど こ?
どこ?
middle.
中
middle?
中?
Inside?
中って?
Inside the bowl.
おわんこの 中
I'm a little sorry.
ちょっとごめんなさい
Digital noise started running,
デジタルノイズが走っちゃったんで、
Look at the camera again.
もう一回ちょっとカメラに向かってね
Please go.
行ってください
Please try again.
もう一回お願いします
Inside the bowl.
おわんこの中
Oh, it's a middle tooth.
あ、中歯なんだ
It's not a chestnut belly.
栗腹じゃないのね
Ah, I see.
あー、なるほどね
That means women can get their fingers in there too.
ということは、女にも指が入っちゃうんだ
In the bowl like this.
おわんこの中にこうやって
hey.
ね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Wow, that's a shame.
うわ、歯立ち
I'd be a little more excited if he was a father.
なんかもうちょっとお父さんだったらドキドキしちゃうね
Yes, yes, yes.
はいはいはい
I like it.
好きなんだ
Yes, I understand.
はい、わかりました
This is important.
これ重要なことなんです
Important things.
重要なこと
I'm not a power harasser.
僕、パワハラじゃないです
This is not power harassment either.
これもうパワハラでもないですよ
It's not sexual harassment either.
セクハラでもないです
This is important right now, for us.
これ今重要なことなんですよ、これ僕たちにとってはね
This is business work.
これビジネスワークですから
That's right.
そんなもんね
Well, let's think about that for a moment.
じゃあちょっとその辺を踏まえてね
Let's try attacking it first.
ちょっとまず攻めてみてみよう
Is it okay?
いいかな?
Thank you for your support.
よろしくお願いしますね
Tameyomi-chan, everyone.
ためよみちゃん、みんな
A naughty chew and a romantic chew,
やらしいチューとロマンチックなチュー、
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Yeah?
うん?
Because it's a big deal.
せっかくだから
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Romantic Chu and Erotic Chu.
ロマンチックなチューとエロいチュー
Eh, romantic.
えー、ロマンチック
Romantic chew?
ロマンチックなチュー?
In the end, I don't even do erotic chews,
結局エロいチューもしないんだけど、
good?
いい?
Naughty.
エッチ
Sexy?
エッチ?
Was it naughty?
エッチだった?
It's already getting harder to fall off just by chewing it.
もうチューしてるだけで落ちにくくなってきちゃった
It's cold.
冷たいね
What should I do? It's big.
どうしたらね、大きいよ
Ah, yes.
あー、そう
Ah, what should I do?
あー、どうしよう
I'll take the one that opens.
開けるの取っちゃうね
Beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおっぱい
Tits.
おつっぱい
Beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおつっぱい
Is this good?
これがいいの?
Is it smooth and beautiful?
なめらめのきれいなの?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Yes, everything tickles at first.
そうだ、なんでも最初はくすぐったいの
Yo.
よ
This is medium skin.
これ、 中肌もんね
But, even though I have medium skin, I have blood.
でもね、中肌だけど、 血をね、
I like how you hold it though.
持 ち方いいんだけど
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
There are no bad kids, right?
悪い子ないでしょ?
Maybe here.
ここにかな、とか
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Yeah?
うん?
delicious?
おいしい?
Yeah.
うん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's delicious.
おいしいね
yeah?
ん?
This is my leg burn.
足やけど、これ
Oh yeah, my leg burns.
そうそう、足やけど
Okay, I'll do this.
いい、これやるやつ
Yeah.
うん
This is now called a demon.
これ、今ね、デーマっていうの
Dema.
デーマ
But, the potation that Dema has,
でもね、デーマが持っているポテーションがね、
I haven't brought it out 100% yet.
まだ100%引き立ててないんですよ
Isn't it still like this?
まだまだ、こんなもんじゃないの、
This dema is.
このデーマは
What do you think?
どうですか?
Don't you know?
わかんない?
So, can you give me a little more power?
じゃあ、もうちょっと力出してもらう?
please.
お願いします
Not yet, not at all.
まだまだ、まだまだ、全然ですよ
Look, this is what it looks like when it's fully opened.
ほら、全開したらこんなんで
No?
ダメ?
Yeah.
うん
All right, go to sleep, go to sleep.
いいじゃん、寝てごらん、寝てごらん
Go to sleep and put your feet together,
寝て、そろそろ、足を寄せてごらん、
It's about time.
そろそろ
oh yeah.
そうそう
It's okay, it's okay.
いいじゃん、いいじゃん
Well then, please send it by yourself.
じゃあ、一人で寄せて
By myself, there.
自分で、そこ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
Isn't it completely visible?
まる見えじゃないですか
Just cut it short, have you seen this?
ちょっと切って、これ見たことある?
From things like this, mine, things like this.
こういうの、自分の、こういうのから
Oh, it's open, it's open.
ああ、開けてる、開けてる
Look, look at this, look at this.
見て、これ見て、見て、これ
Do you understand?
わかる?
Look, look, this.
見て、見て、これ
Can you swim with mango by yourself?
自分でマンゴー泳げてんの
copper?
どう?
Naughty.
エッチ
That's naughty.
エッチだね
Hey, sex isn't hot.
ね、エッチは熱めしないね
Yes, yes, do you want to?
はい、はい、しますか
I'm talking picha picha.
ピチャピチャ言ってる
Yeah.
うん
I'm talking picha picha.
ピチャピチャ言ってるよ
Yeah.
うん
I'm talking picha picha.
ピチャピチャ言ってるよ
why?
なんで?
Why are you talking so loud?
なんでピチャピチャ言ってるの?
Because it feels good.
気 持 ちいいから
Because it feels good?
気持ちいいから?
I see, I see.
そっか、そっか
Just in case, I don't know about Nakahara.
一応ね、中原ののは分かってないけどね
Because they're coming from here to there.
あっちからあっちに来てるからね
It's not that I feel bad about being stuck with just Nakahara.
中原だけで別にくっついてるのが気持ち悪いわけじゃないもんね
It feels good, it feels good.
気持ちいいこと気持ちいいんだよね
Yeah.
うん
That's important.
そこ重要だね
Yeah.
うん
copper?
どう?
Can I continue a little longer?
もうちょっと続けていい?
Where are you going?
どこへ行っちゃう?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
It's okay, you can go to sleep.
いいよ、寝ちゃっていいよ
It's okay to let go.
手も離したっていいよ
It would be helpful if you just opened your legs.
足だけ開いてくれたらおじさん助かるなぁ
Yes, just your legs hanging out.
そう、足だけぶらぶら
what up?
どうした?
Are you going?
行っちゃうの?
You can go.
行っていいよ
行 って いいよ
show me.
見せて
Show me where you went.
行ったところ見せて
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?
行っちゃったの?
Which one?
どっちどっち?
Have you gone?
行っちゃったの?
行っちゃった?
You can go, right?
行けるんじゃん?
行けるんじゃないですか?
You can go right away, right?
すぐ行けちゃうじゃないですか?
Did you open it?
開けちゃった?
開けちゃったの?
Hot hot.
熱い熱い
I'm leaving you alone.
ほってってるよ
It feels good, doesn't it?
気持ちいいじゃないですかね?
Yeah yeah yeah.
うんうんうん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's a push push.
プシュプシュだね
Is it going up?
上がってる?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気 持ちいい?
My curiosity is pushed.
好奇心が押せられる
Isn't it pushy?
プシュプシュじゃないですか?
You have a beautiful body.
綺麗な体してるね
I want to flow around forever.
ずっと流れ回したい
Did you get a little bored?
ちょっとくすずったりしたの?
It's the bones of Apara.
アパラの骨じゃん
Doesn't it feel good to have been doing this for so long?
こう やってずっとやったこと気持ちよくない?
Today, it's not just a nuisance, it's a new discovery.
ちょっと今日ね、いじわじゃなくて 新しい発見ね
It's like a new discovery.
新しい発見等しいから
I wonder if anyone goes here?
ここに行く人いるのかな?
By the way, let me tell you.
ちなみに言っとけよ
Isn't it like this?
こういう感じじゃない?
feet
足
Hold your neck on both sides.
を ね、首をね、両側して挟んで
Isn't it fun?
楽しいでしょ?
What's going on?
どうなってる?
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってる
Has the old man arrived yet?
おじいさんが着きなの?
And in the morning
そして朝、
I want you to feel good, but
気 持ちよくしてほしいんだけど、
Isn't it a mask?
マスクじゃない?
What should I do with my mask?
マ スクをさ、どうしよう?
Let's be gathered by the nose.
鼻に集められていこう
Just show your mouth, and show your eyes and mouth.
口だけ出して、 目と口を出す
That's right, that's right.
そうです、そうです
Maybe, just a little weird looking.
多分ね、ちょっとね、 見た目は変だけどね
Because this is the only solution.
これしか解決方法がないからね
Well then, I'm going to get some sleep, so wake up.
じゃあ、ちょっと寝るから起きてほら
I'm going to sleep in bed.
ベッドに寝るよ
Ah, yes.
あー、そう
Look here, once.
こっち見てほら、一回
The mask is interesting.
マスク面白い
Well then, keep your mouth shut.
じゃあ、口もちょくして
Who is this behind?
これは誰の後ろなの?
Second?
2番目?
1st?
1番目?
Number 1.
1番
That's amazing, he was such an erotic high school student.
すごいね、エロい高校生だったんだね
You've seen too many harsh things.
エグいの見過ぎだね
My fingertips are cool and feel good.
指先がね、ひやっこくて気持ちいい
Hey, right?
平正でしょ?
completely peaceful
全く平正で
Sho?
しょ?
Ah, that's embarrassing.
あー、 恥ずかしい
You don't really play around, do you?
あ んま遊んでないでしょ?
There are people who don't play as much as you imagine, right?
想像より遊んでない人ってでしょ?
It's heavy.
重いじゃん
Ah, yes.
あー、そう
Looking at the camera.
カメラ目線で
Ah, yes.
あー、そう
Ah, this way.
あー、こっち
What is this, Soultouch?
なんだこの、ソウルトタッチが
I love you so much, right?
俺は超好きでしょ?
This kind of soul touch can last quite a long time.
こういうソウルトタッチだと、 結構長い時間させられちゃいます
Yo.
よ
Isn't it quite a long time?
結 構長い時間しない?
do not have?
ない?
be?
ある?
Why now?
今どうして?
Are you punishing me?
制裁してるの?
Would you like to stretch your legs?
足伸ばしてごらん?
Try lying face down.
うつ伏せみたいになってごらん?
oh yeah.
そう、そう
And it's easy to face the camera.
そして 顔がカメラを向きやすいでしょ
Ah, yes.
あー、そう
What's going on with your penis?
おちんちん、どうなってる?
Tick-tock.
カチカチ
It's getting hard.
硬くなってる
Is it ticking?
カ チカチになってる?
I want to shake.
揺れたい
So get on top.
じゃあ、上に乗って
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Oh, it's so narrow.
あー、すっごい狭い
Not told?
言われない?
Are you excited?
くりくりするの?
Not up and down, but back and forth.
上下じゃなくて、前後に
Ah, yes.
あー、そう
Do you understand?
分かる?
It's a hit, right?
当たるでしょ?
Around here.
この辺に
It's quite aggressive.
結構アグレッシブだね
Amazing, amazing.
すっごい、すっごい
This will make your dick swell.
チンポもげるよ、これ
When did I remember this?
いつ覚えたの、こんなの
It's like a special move.
必殺技みたい
Isn't anyone going to this?
これ、行っちゃう人いない?
I'm going.
行っちゃう
Let's go, right?
行っちゃうでしょ、これ
This, this first.
これ、最初にこれ
I was about to say something.
なんか言いかけた
Also, if I did something like this the first time,
あと、最初にこんなことやってたら、
It's a rough start and a rough finish.
スタートがきじょいできじょいで終わっちゃうね
A difficult start doesn't end in a difficult way.
きじょいスタートがきじょいで終わんない
Isn't it over?
終わんない?
It'll end, right?
終わるでしょ
And it's a hit.
しかも当たる
I love the inside so much.
すっごい奥大好きなのね
Is it okay?
よいしょ?
Do you like bags?
バック好き?
Well, let's do the back next time.
じゃあ、次バックやろうか
So, put your hands on me, put your hands on me.
じゃあ、手置いて、手置いて
Pull it out slowly.
ゆっくり抜いて
Turn your butt towards the camera.
お尻をカメラによけて
Come on, come on, come on.
さあ、さあ、さあ
Wow, my pussy is soaked.
うわ、マンコビショビショだよ
It's shiny, look.
テカテカだよ、ほら
It's shiny.
テカテカだよ
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
This is Manjul, Manjul.
これマンジュルですよ、マンジュル
no doubt.
間違いない
Do you understand?
わかる?
It's so tense.
ピチョチョになってる
Do you understand?
わかる?
You're a pussy.
あなたはマンコですよ
Come on, come on, come on.
さあ、さあ、さあ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Should I go out?
出ちゃおうかな
Do you understand?
わかる?
Do you know what's bothering you?
おかされてるのわかる?
I'm being fooled.
おかされてるんだよ
It feels good, right?
気持ちよいでしょ?
She has a great pussy.
すごいマンコしてるよ
Did you hear?
聞いた?
Pussy.
マンコ
I watch it to laugh.
笑うために見てるよ
uncle.
おじさん
Does your uncle feel good?
おじさんの気持ちいい?
Uncle feels good.
おじさんの気持ちいい
Tell me that your uncle's cock feels good.
おじさんのチンポが気持ちいいって言って
My uncle's cock feels good.
おじさんのチンポが気持ちいい
Don't eat cake anyway.
どうせケーキを食べないで
What number is it from the top?
上から何番ね?
Falling place.
落ち場
A place to fall?
落ち場?
There.
そこね
I think it's Prisher.
プリッシャーだと思う
Is that about it?
それぐらいなの?
Okay.
いいよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
If you recognize me, call me, old man.
認識したら呼んでくれ、おじさんの子
Which one?
どっち?
Will you call me?
呼んでくれる?
I'll put it out.
出すよ
Okay.
よし
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様でした
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Please wake up the shadow.
影を起こしてください
A lot of flowing water.
いっぱい流らし
What do you think?
どうですか?
Where is it?
ど こだ?
Was it washed away?
流らしされたとか
Isn't it spilling?
こぼれてない?
It's okay.
大丈夫ですね
How was it?
どうでした?
What do you think?
感想は?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
I'm the third guy, but is it okay if I say he feels the best?
3番目の男ですけど、 一番気持ちいいってことでいいですか?
It's not like I'm forcing it.
無理やりはしてるわけじゃないですからね
If it's different, it's fine.
違ったら違ったらいいんですよ
it was good.
良かった
I wonder if I can play with you again.
また遊んでもらおうかな
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
I mean, it felt good.
気持ちよかったってことでね
If it feels good, give a V sign.
気持ちよかったらVサインを1つ
If it feels really good, give me a double V sign.
とっても気持ちよかったら ダブルVサインでね
please.
お願いします
どう ぞ
I received a double V sign.
ダブルVサイン頂きました
I received two V signs.
Vサイン2つ頂きました
thank you.
ありがとうございます